<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>azurata.me</title><link>https://www.azurata.me/</link><description>Recent content on azurata.me</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.azurata.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.azurata.me/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.azurata.me/about/</guid><description>Profile I&amp;rsquo;m a student learning computer science in Future University Hakodate since April 2021.
In former, I was learning in prefectural high school in Okinawa, Japan until March 2021.
I&amp;rsquo;m interested in ubiquitous computing and entertainment systems with it.
Skills Web Frontend ITRON Application Awards ET Software Design Robot Contest 2019 in Okinawa, Grand Champion Qualified IT Passport(National exam in Japan) Cisco Networking Academy CCNA R&amp;amp;S: Introduction to Networks CCNA R&amp;amp;S: Routing and Switching Essentials Introduction to Cybersecurity</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://www.azurata.me/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.azurata.me/history/</guid><description>2002 Born in Okinawa, Japan. 2018 Entered prefectural high school in Okinawa. Began to study about Application Software. 2019 Got CCNA R&amp;amp;S: Introduction to Networks Got Grand Champion of ET Software Design Robot Contest 2019 in Okinawa 2020 Got IT Passport Got CCNA R&amp;amp;S: Routing and Switching Essentials Got Introduction to Cybersecurity Contributed to Code-for-OKINAWA/covid19 2021 Entered Future University Hakodate</description></item><item><title>Weekly azurata ~8/27</title><link>https://www.azurata.me/posts/weekly-08-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.azurata.me/posts/weekly-08-27/</guid><description>やったこと 集中講義受けた モデル図書き終えた ちょっとだけETロボコンのプログラム進めた 今年の経験を踏まえて来年のETロボコンをどう進めるか書き出してみた わかったこと エントリー参加者にはLinuxとかWSLの話から始めるべきかも 締め切りギリギリに成果物を作り始めない つぎやること ETロボコンのプログラムの作成 とりあえずPID制御で走るまで 運動する</description></item><item><title>個人向けWikiシステムの考察</title><link>https://www.azurata.me/posts/2021-08-12-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.azurata.me/posts/2021-08-12-00/</guid><description>Boost Note ほぼGitHub Markdown．昔は今でいうLocal Storageのみしか使えなかったのでGitHubやOneDriveなどを利用していた．今は公式が共有する手段を用意しているが，使いづらい
Scrapbox Markdownで書けないのが好みではない
Notion 現状ベスト．挙動が怪しいところがあるものの，Markdownで書けるうえ機能もモリモリ</description></item></channel></rss>